Mihai Elisei JUNIOR FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Phone No.: +353 (0)89 276 1806 Email: mihai.m.elisei@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mihai-elisei-48ba87a7/

GitHub: https://github.com/MihaiElisei

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly motivated and organized individual, committed to excellent service with the ability to multitask at the highest level. Flexible work ethic with 5+ years' experience within the IT sector, delivering a quality service with integrity. Strong organizational and time management skills. Highly computer literate with the ability to learn and absorb technical details and systems very quickly. Presently upskilling to further career in a role as a junior software developer.

KEY SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python.

Databases: MySQL
 Version Control: GitHub, Git
 Frameworks: Bootstrap

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

September 2022 – present Technological University Dublin

Bsc. in Information Technology and Information Systems

April 2022 – present Code Institute

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development (E-Commerce) Credit Rated by The University of the West of Scotland

September 2008 – august 2010 Advanced/Higher Certificate in Mechanic Foreman

Military school of warrant officers of the Romanian Naval Forces

Constanta Romania

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

https://mihaielisei.github.io/Mihai-Elisei/

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2022 – present IT Support Engineer, Convergint Technologies, Dublin, Ireland

- Installation and Commissioning of Cameras, controllers, panels, sensors, & devices;
- Overlook the project installation and making sure that it meets the technical design;
- Data entry and programming in various cloud based applications;

Dec 2021 – May 2022 Field Engineer, Actavo, Dublin, Ireland

 Install and service cabling infrastructure and devices for Data, Audio Visual, and CCTV; includes prewiring, installation, termination, testing, reporting, and labelling per specifications and drawings;

- Interact with customers and prospects, ensuring all inquiries are handled professionally;
- Perform additional duties and projects as assigned;

September 2017 – October 2021

IT Technician, Ministry of Justice Romania National Administration of Penitentiaries.

- Install and service cabling infrastructure and devices for Data, Audio Visual, and CCTV; includes prewiring, installation, termination, testing, reporting, and labelling per specifications and drawings;
- Test Quality of lines, as well as broadband quality;
- Used good problem-solving skills for troubleshooting problems;
- Administration of Windows based applications of basic principles, theories, and concepts;
- Speak and communicate effectively with other members of the jobsite crew;

August 2010 – August 2017

Warrant Officer Romanian Navy

- Interactive communication;
- Performing high productivity processing, assembly of machine tools;
- Checking products quality;
- Providing the observance of the occupational protection norms and firefighting norms;

CERTIFICATES

- Udemy Complete JavaScript (40/69 hours)
- Udemy The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp (10/20 hours)
- Udemy React-The complete guide(incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)(5/48 hours)
- Pirple Python3 Fundamentals (3/16 hours)

_

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Currently learning Python Code Institute;
- By the end of the course with Code Institute I will learn Flask, Django, SQL, jQuery, API's and more;
- I have enrolled for C++ and C# courses on Pirple platform;
- Languages: Fluent English;